(Man:)Not always. A box fell on my
head at UPS six years ago.
(Man:)Now I just collect disability
and ride trains.
(Amy:)-Why do I even try?
-I'm gonna fix this right now.
OK. Just make it
look like an accident.
(Bernadette:)Excuse me. You are at Valentine's
dinner with your girlfriend.
(Bernadette:)Now get back over there
and be with her.
(Sheldon:)You're right.
That was insensitive of me.
(Sheldon:)I have to go back to my table now.
(Sheldon:)-You should join us.
-All right.
(Bernadette:)Great. Now there's two of 'em.
(Lady Vet:)-How much chocolate did she eat?
-A whole box.
(Leonard:)Well, to be fair, you ate a lot of it
before you gave it to me.
(Penny:)So the point is I may
have saved her life.